Inventory of the Victoria Schuck papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Victoria Schuck papers
1956-1977
98064
Hoover Institution Archives
15 manuscript boxes, 3 oversize boxes, 1 oversize folder (7.6 linear feet)
The bulk of the collection spans from 1961 to 1977, mainly while Schuck was a professor of the Political Science Department at Mount Holyoke College. The collection primarily reflects Schuck's research interests in South Vietnam: elections, government administration, the Vietnam War, the case of Tran Ngoc Chau, and the South Vietnam Youth Movement. The collection is composed of writings, statistical data, biographical data, publications, photographs, and other materials.
Schuck, Victoria
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1998.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
16 March 1909 Born in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma.
1930 Received Bachelor of Arts degree from Stanford University.
1931 Received Master of Arts degree at Stanford University.
1937 Received Doctor of Philosophy degree at Stanford University.
1937-1940 Assistant Professor at Florida State College for Women.
1940-1976 Member of the Mount Holyoke College Political Science Department.
1942-1944 Worked as the Principal Program Analyst for the Office of Price Administration.
1945-1947 Served as a consultant at the Office of Temporary Controls.
1948-1949 Visiting lecturer at Smith College.
1948-1974 Served on the Lecture Committee at Mount Holyoke College.
1949 Initiated a Washington Internship Program.
1952 Visiting professor at Stanford University.
1954 Established a Political Studies Center.
1957-1960 A member of the Massachusetts Commission on Interstate Cooperation.
1958-1965 A member of the Board of Trustees of the University of Massachusetts.
1960-1962 Served on the Honors Committee at Mount Holyoke College.
1960-1968 A member of the University's Building Authority.
1961-1967 A member of the Town of South Hadley, Massachusetts Planning Board.
1962-1974 A member of the Massachusetts Advisory Committee to the United States Commission on Civil Rights.
1963 President John F. Kennedy appointed her as a member of the President's Commission on Registration and Voting Participation.
1964-1973 A member of the Berkshire Community College New Campus Committee.
1966 In South Vietnam under a grant from the Four-College Asian and African Studies Committee to conduct research on innovations in the civil service and budgeting.
1966, 1971 Received grants to observe elections in South Vietnam and to study the Vietnamese constitution.
1967-1968 A visiting scholar at the Brookings Institute.
1971-1972 Vice President of the American Political Science Association.
1972-1973 President of the Northeastern Political Science Association.
1974 Retired from full-time teaching at Mount Holyoke College.
1975-1976 Returned to teach Winter Term courses at Mount Holyoke College.
1977-1980 Served as President of Mount Vernon College in Washington, D.C.
1980 Received an honorary degree from Mount Vernon College upon retirement.
1988 "The American Political Science Association established an annual award in her name to be given to the author of a book on women and politics."
15 February 1999 Died in Chevy Chase, Maryland.
Sources: "Constitution-Making in Vietnam--A Part of 'The Other War'" by Victoria Schuck for the Mount Holyoke Alumnae Quarterly, Summer 1967
Biographical Note, Victoria Schuck Papers Finding Aid, 1930-1999, Mount Holyoke College Archives and Special Collections, Mount Holyoke College, South Hadley, Massachusetts.
Scope and Content of Collection
Collection spans from 1956 to 1977, collected primarily while Schuck was a Political Science professor at Mount Holyoke College. The collection reflects Schuck's research interests in South Vietnam: elections, government administration, the Vietnam War, the case of Tran Ngoc Chau, and the South Vietnam Youth Movement, among other topics. The collection is composed of writings, statistical data, biographical data, publications, photographs, and other materials.
The Research file is organized into the three categories: Vietnam Youth Movement materials, photographs from trips of Schuck and Jim Mott, and Tran Ngoc Chau documents, along with materials related generally to Vietnam and Southeast Asia. The Research file also includes materials on the Vietnam War, government administration, and South Vietnam elections, among other topics.
The South Vietnam Elections file contains documents related to Schuck’s research, organized into the following categories: General file, National Assembly and Constituent Assembly file, Upper House file, Lower House file, President and Vice President file, and Senate file. These categories include news releases, posters, decrees, statistical data, and other materials pertaining to general elections, village and hamlet elections, assembly elections, Upper House and Lower House elections, presidential elections, and senatorial elections.
The Vietnam Government Administration file includes a Constitution file, along with materials that include documents, charts, maps, and other items related to the government and administration of Vietnam. More specific topics include village government, hamlet government, military government, local government, and regional government.
The Vietnam War f ile includes documents, charts, maps, news releases, and other materials related to the Vietnam War. More specifically, topics include Vietcong, U.S. military assistance, Land-to-the-Tiller, and peace.
Related Collection(s)
Victoria Schuck papers, 1930-1999, Mount Holyoke College Archives and Special Collections.
Victoria Schuck papers, circa 1974-1980, Special Collections Research Center, Gelman Library, The George Washington University.
Elections--Vietnam.; Legislative bodies--Vietnam.; United States--Foreign relations--Vietnam.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Vietnam--Foreign relations--United States.; Vietnam--Politics and government--1945-1975.
- Research File, 1961-1977
  Scope and Contents note
  Comprised of bulletins, newspaper clippings, magazines, and press releases that touch upon the Vietnam War, South Vietnam elections, and government administration. Additionally incldues materials on the Vietnam Youth Movement, photographs of Southeast Asia, and the Tran Ngoc Chau's case. Arranged chronologically.
  - The New Leader magazine, 1961 June 5 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Park Avenue Social Review, 1963 (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Maps, 1964, 1965, 1970 (Box-folder 1: 3)
    "Viet Nam Cambodia, Laos and Eastern Thailand," "Republic of Vietnam," "Saigon and Vicinity", and "Map of Region 1 South Vietnam."
  - Current History A Monthly Magazine of World Affairs, 1964 February (Box-folder 1: 4)
    Magazine has articles related to South and Southeast Asia.
  - "Administration of the Government of Thailand," poster, 1964 (Map case)
    Formerly in Box/Folder 13: 1
  - Brochures, 1964-1973, undated (Box-folder 1: 5)
    Materials focused on Saigon, Exposition Vany (mainly Vietnamese), Vietnam retrospective symposium at Amherst College, and Vietnam.
  - Personal and public security documents, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Vietnam-American relations, 1965 (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Edward Landsdale articles, 1965 (Box-folder 1: 8)
  - Information Brief Tay Ninh Province Viet Nam with related Vietnamese documents, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 1: 9)
  - The Vietnamese Women Association packet, circa 1965 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Addresses by Charles A. Mann and General Charles De Gaulle, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 1: 11)
  - "Duc Duc District Under our Eyes,", 1965 (Box-folder 1: 12)
  - Vietnam Youth Movement Materials, 1965-1967
    Materials include memoranda, briefings, English translations from Vietnamese news magazines, and other items about the Summer Youth Program, the Vietnamese Youth Movement.
    - Summer Youth Program memoranda, 1965, undated (Box-folder 10: 1)
    - Briefings, 1965, undated (Box-folder 10: 2)
    - Vietnamese youth, 1965 (Box-folder 10: 3)
      Comprised of materials regarding youth studying in France, and Summer Youth Program general documents.
    - English translations from Weekly Len Duong, 1965 (Box-folder 10: 4)
    - English translations not from Weekly Len Duong, 1965 (Box-folder 10: 5)
    - English translations from magazines, 1965 (Box-folder 10: 6)
    - "Minutes of the Fifth Meeting of the Civilian Manpower Committee,", 1966 (Box-folder 10: 7)
      Includes employment opportunities for students during summer months.
    - Charles Sweet writings, 1966 (Box-folder 10: 8)
      Contains "The Role of Youth in the Revolutionary Development Program," drafts, handwritten notes of Ministry of Revolutionary Development Survey, and "Youth and Sports Program FY 1966."
    - Reports and papers primarily about youth programs, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 10: 9)
  - Life in Vietnam The Weekly News Magazine, 1966 May 28 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - News in Brief about Tuy Hoa, Quang Ngai, and Hue, 1966 September 15 (Box-folder 1: 16)
  - Government of Vietnam "Concepts of Rural Construction" paper, 1966 February 21 (Box-folder 1: 17)
  - New York Herald Tribune commentary on events, 1966 (Box-folder 1: 18)
  - Government decrees, revolutionary cadre, and land reform, 1966 (Box-folder 1: 19)
  - USAID Functional Directory and General Information with inserts, 1966 (Box-folder 1: 20)
  - Miss Sunyee's paintings, two books in Chinese, 1966 (Box-folder 1: 21)
  - News Clippings, 1966-1974, undated (Box-folder 1: 22)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - The Outline of Caodaism, 1966 July 18 (Box-folder 2: 2)
  - VIETNAM: WHY A Collection of Reports And Comment From THE REPORTER about China, Vietnam, Thailand, and Buddhists, 1966 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Vietnam documents, including letters, handwritten notes, Government of Vietnam Provincial Budget Fiscal Year 1965 book, and dinner invitation, 1966 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Buddhists news releases, circa 1966 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Manpower documents, 1966 (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Fiscal future news release, 1966 (Box-folder 2: 7)
  - Free World AID to [Viet Nam] Newsletter, 1966 (Box-folder 2: 8)
  - Photographs, 1966, undated
    Comprised of photographic slides from Southeast Asia trip, and photographs that Jim Mott took on his trip to Saigon.
    - Photographic slides from Southeast Asia trip, 1966 (Box-folder 1: 14-15)
      Slides document her stops in Phnom Penh, Hawaii, Hong Kong, India, Japan, Kuala Lumpur, Philippines, Moscow, Bangkok, and Saigon.
    - Jim Mott trip to Saigon, undated (Box-folder 10: 10-16)
    - Unidentified temple, undated (Box-folder 10: 17)
  - Handwritten notes, 1966-1967, undated (Box-folder 2: 9)
  - The Department of State Publication, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 2: 10)
  - Veterans documents, 1967, undated (Box-folder 2: 11)
  - Mount Holyoke Alumnae Quarterly, 1967 (Box-folder 2: 12)
    Includes Schuck's article "Constitution-Making in Vietnam--A Part of 'The Other War.'"
  - Saigon Press Analysis Of Vietnamese and Chinese Dailies, 1967 April-June (Box-folder 2: 13)
  - Vietnampress with handwritten notes, 10 June 1967 (Box-folder 2: 14)
  - "Who Moonlights and Why?,", 1967 (Box-folder 2: 15)
  - U.S. Agency for International Development Mission to Vietnam Schedule of Events for Ernest W. McFarland and wife, Mr. and Mrs. Leon Nowell, and Mr. and Mrs. Ralph Watkins, 1967 August 16-20 (Box-folder 2: 16)
  - Letter in Vietnamese, 1967 (Box-folder 2: 17)
  - Who's Who in Vietnam, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 11: 1-4)
  - Viet-Nam Bulletin, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 2: 18-22)
  - Viet-Nam Bulletin, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3: 1-2)
  - Supreme Court rulings and decisions, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 14: 24)
    Includes ruling on the Saigon City Council's Resolution of 11 August 1969, Supreme Court decisions about Tran Ngoc Chau, and the constitution.
  - Tran Ngoc Chau Documents, 1969-1970
    Documents contain Tran Ngoc Chau's statements, Tran Ngoc Hien's self-confession regarding Tran Ngoc Chau, news releases and articles, writings in Vietnamese, and Supreme Court decisions. Documents include details related to Tran Ngoc Chau's beliefs about Communists and methods of achieving peace while he was Secretary General of South Viethnam's Lower House. Materials also cover Tran Ngoc Chau's prison case.
    - "An Open Letter of Deputy Tran Ngoc Chau" given after "The President's Biased Accusations Against [his] Person and The Threats [The President] Made in Vung Tau Against The National Assembly,", 1969 (Box-folder 9: 14)
    - "Not Gone With the Wind" statement by Tran Ngoc Chau about "Why Must We Talk with North Vietnam and the National Liberation Front,", 1969 (Box-folder 9: 15)
    - "Self-Confession by Tran Ngoc Hien in Relation to Tran Ngoc Chau," and "Extract from the Self-Confession of Tran-Ngoc-Hien Concerning Tran-Ngoc-Chau,", circa 1969 (Box-folder 9: 16)
    - "Circumstances Surrounding Tran Ngoc Chau's Imprisonment and Activities,", 1969-1970 (Box-folder 9: 17-18)
    - "Details About Aftermath of Tran Ngoc Chau's Imprisonment and his Biographical Summary,", 1970 (Box-folder 9: 19)
    - "Details About Tran Ngoc Chau's Prison Case,", 1970 (Box-folder 9: 20)
    - "Declaration of Deputy Tran Ngoc Chau,", 1970 (Box-folder 9: 21)
    - "Tran Ngoc Chau's Imprisonment and What Led Him to Prison,", circa 1970 (Box-folder 9: 22)
    - "The Story of Tran Ngoc Chau," article from Congressional Record - Senate, 1970 February 5 (Box-folder 9: 23)
    - Writings in Vietnamese, 1970 (Box-folder 9: 24)
    - Tran Ngoc Chau's case, Supreme Court decisions, 1970 (Box-folder 9: 25)
  - Vietnam Statistical Yearbook, 1970 (Box-folder 3: 3)
  - Documents in Vietnamese, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - South Vietnam Provincial Maps book, 1971 April (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Embassy of the United States of America and Joint United States Public Affairs Office Telephone Directory Saigon, 1971 July (Box-folder 3: 6)
  - Customs and Manners in South Vietnam Through Some Rhymes of Folk Songs, 1971 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - News release in Vietnamese, 1971 (Box-folder 3: 9)
  - List in Vietnamese, 1971 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - "Inauguration Ceremony of President Nguyen Van Thieu,", 1971 (Box-folder 3: 11)
  - Bibliographies on Vietnam from Goodman essays and from thesis, 1971 (Box-folder 3: 12)
  - Newspaper in Vietnamese, 1971 (Box-folder 3: 13)
  - Southeast Asia An International Quarterly, 1971 (Box-folder 3: 14)
  - Agenda for Victoria Schuck in Washington, D.C., 1971 December 17 (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - The Fourth Buddhist General Meeting, 1971 (Box-folder 4: 2)
  - The New Yorker, articles about Korea, 1972 (Box-folder 4: 3)
  - The New Yorker, "Letter from Washington,", 1972-1973 (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - "Fizzle in the Lake,", 1973 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - "Dean Rusk and Southeast Asia: An Operational Code Analysis,", 1973 (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - The New Yorker, "Annals of Finance,", 1973 (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - Freedom at Issue, 1973 September-October (Box-folder 4: 7)
  - The New Yorker, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 4: 8)
  - The New Yorker, 14 January 1974 (Box-folder 4: 9)
  - Time magazine, 1975 April 15 (Box-folder 4: 10)
  - Time magazine, 1975 May 5 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Congressional Quarterly Weekly Report, 1975 February 15 - March 8 (Box-folder 4: 12)
  - The New York Review of Books newspaper, 1976 July 15 (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - "How Carter will Differ from Ford - An Expert's View," article from U.S. News & World Report, photocopy, 1977 (Box-folder 4: 14)
  - Ford Foundation Letter excerpts, 1977 February 1 (Box-folder 4: 15)
  - Vietnam Bulletin, Indochina notes, undated (Box-folder 4: 16)
  - Huong Que, undated (Box-folder 4: 17)
  - "Experiment in District Eight,", undated (Box-folder 4: 18)
  - Phone and address list, undated (Box-folder 4: 19)
  - Directories in Vietnamese, undated (Box-folder 4: 20)
  - "List of Ladies Attending the Tea Given on Thursday October 14th at 4pm,", undated (Box-folder 4: 21)
  - Documents in Vietnamese, undated (Box-folder 4: 22)
  - Headshots with descriptions in Vietnamese, undated (Box-folder 4: 23)
  - Map of Thailand and Laos, undated (Map case)
    Formerly in Box/Folder 5: 2.
  - Address and telephone directory, undated (Box-folder 5: 3)
  - "Common Foods in Viet-Nam,", undated (Box-folder 5: 4)
  - Cover in Vietnamese, photocopy from original, undated (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - "Bleak Prospects for Afro-Asian Council Meeting" from News Analysis, undated (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - "Viet Nam Insight, A Vietnamese Looks at Vietnam" paper, undated (Box-folder 5: 7)
  - Bibliography, undated (Box-folder 5: 8)
  - "Vietnam," description documents, undated (Box-folder 5: 9)
  - A Nation's Progress The Story of U.S. - Vietnamese Cooperation in Economic Development, undated (Box-folder 5: 10)
  - "Discussion of the Conception of a New Deportment,", undated (Box-folder 5: 11)
  - Poster from Air Vietnam, undated (Box-folder 5: 12)
- South Vietnam Elections File, 1963-1973
  Includes decrees, news clippings, statistical data, lists, and other materials related to South Vietnam elections in general, including village and hamlet elections, regarding Vietnam’s National Assembly and Constituent Assembly, Upper House, Lower House, President and Vice-President, and Senate.
  - General file, 1964-1973
    File includes decrees, news clippings, lists, posters, election results, and other materials related to South Vietnam's elections and voting in general, which consists of a mix of information about National Assembly, Upper House, Lower House, president, vice president, senate, village, and hamlet.
    - Village and Hamlet elections decrees, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 5: 13)
    - Elections news clippings and documents, photocopies, 1964-1966, undated (Box-folder 5: 14)
    - "Elections of Prefectural, Provincial and Municipal Councils (data presented by the Under Secretary of State for Interior)," document, English translation, 1965 May 5 (Box-folder 5: 15)
    - "National Congress Election Law,", 1965 January 31 (Box-folder 5: 16)
    - Elections news clippings, 1966 (Box-folder 5: 17)
    - "Members of the Electoral Law Committee," list, 1966 (Box-folder 5: 18)
    - Elections, handwritten notes, 1966 (Box-folder 5: 19)
    - Elections news releases, circa 1966 (Box-folder 5: 20-21)
    - List of elected persons, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 5: 22)
    - Elections, mixed documents and handwritten notes, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 5: 23)
    - Posters in Vietnamese, 1967 (Map case)
      Formerly in Box/Folder 5: 24 and Box/Folder 13: 3
    - "Background Papers on the Elections in Vietnam,", 1967 (Box-folder 5: 25)
    - "Vietnamese Election Results,", 1967 (Box-folder 5: 26)
    - Election list in Vietnamese, circa 1967 (Box-folder 5: 27)
    - "Comparative Election Statistics,", circa 1967 (Box-folder 5: 28)
    - Short biographies, book in Vietnamese, 1967 (Box-folder 5: 29)
    - "Notes on the Administration of Elections in South Vietnam" paper, 1967 (Box-folder 5: 30)
    - Banners in Vietnamese, 1967 (Box-folder 6: 1)
    - "What to do During the Election Period" document, 1967 (Box-folder 6: 2)
    - Election results documents, 1967 (Box-folder 6: 3)
    - Comic book in Vietnamese, circa 1967 (Box-folder 6: 4)
    - Importance of the coming elections, poster in Vietnamese with English description, 1967 (Box-folder 6: 5)
    - "1967 Village and Hamlet Elections," (Box-folder 7: 1)
    - Map and election results, 1967 (Box-folder 7: 2)
    - "Presidential, Vice-Presidential, Senatorial Election Schedule 1967," (Box-folder 8: 22)
    - "Excerpts from Vietnam Statistical Yearbook - 1967-1968," in English and in Vietnamese (Box-folder 7: 3)
    - Public Administration Bulletin Vietnam, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 6: 6-7, Box-folder 7: 6)
    - "Systems Analysis for the Vietnam Study" memorandum, 1968 (Box-folder 7: 4)
    - Directory in Vietnamese, 1971 (Box-folder 7: 7)
    - List of constituents, 1971 (Box-folder 6: 9)
    - "South Vietnam will elect more Supreme Court Justices" from Vietnam Feature Service, 1971 May (Box-folder 6: 10)
    - "Deputies Whose Credentials were Challenged -- 23 deputies" document, 1978 Spetember 28 (Box-folder 7: 8)
    - Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group (SEADAG) papers and documents, 1971 (Box-folder 6: 11-13)
    - Hamlet evaluation tables, 1971 (Box 18)
    - Election reports, 1973 (Box-folder 6: 14)
    - Election press release, 1973 (Box-folder 6: 15)
    - The New Yorker cover, 1973 October 15 (Box-folder 6: 16)
    - "Vietnam Political Development Statistics" document, undated (Box-folder 6: 17)
    - "Full Text of the Letter from Senator Henry Jackson to President Nixon,", undated (Box-folder 6: 18)
    - Handwritten notes, undated (Box-folder 6: 19)
    - List of deputies, undated (Box-folder 7: 9)
    - Headshots of officials, in Vietnamese, photocopies of newspapers, undated (Box-folder 7: 10)
    - Codebook "Vietnamese Elite Inventory for Winners and Losers of Eight National Elections 1956-1971,", undated (Box-folder 7: 11)
    - "Vietnamese Officials,", undated (Box-folder 7: 12)
    - "Cross Classification of Responses to Selected Questions,", undated (Box-folder 12: 7)
  - National Assembly and Constituent Assembly File, 1963-1971
    File consists of documents and statistical data related to the National Assembly and Constitutent Assembly elections.
    - "Summary of National Assembly Election,", 1963 (Box-folder 7: 25)
    - "Buddhists Call Fast to Protest Election" article from Vietnam Roundup, 1966 September 7 (Box-folder 7: 26)
    - "Groupings of Delegates to the 1966 Constituent Assembly," (Box-folder 7: 27)
    - National Constitutent Assembly Election handbook, 1966 (Box-folder 7: 28)
    - "List of Candidates to the Constituent Assembly Election" from Vietnampress, 1966 August 22 (Box-folder 7: 29)
    - "List of Candidates for the Constituent Assembly Election,", 1966 September 11 (Box-folder 7: 30)
    - Assembly election documents, 1966 (Box-folder 7: 31)
    - National Constituent Assemble Election reference handbook, photocopy, 1966 (Box-folder 8: 1)
    - "Central Government: How Highlanders and Chams Will Be Represented in the Constituent Assembly,", 1966 (Box-folder 8: 2)
    - "Constituent Assembly Elections in South Viet-Nam,", circa 1966, undated (Box-folder 8: 3)
    - "Constituent Assembly Election Results,", 1966 (Box-folder 8: 4)
    - Constituent Assembly Elections data booklet, handwritten, 1966 September 11 (Box-folder 8: 5)
    - Official Journal of the Republic of Vietnam, 8 parts in series, 1966-1967
      Original Vietnamese newspapers in Box 12, English translations in box 8, 15 and 17.
      - Part 1, 1966 December 5 (Box-folder 12: 1, Box-folder 17: 17)
      - Part 2, 1966 December 12 (Box-folder 12: 2, Box-folder 17: 18)
      - Part 3-4, English translations, 1967 January 16 (Box-folder 8: 7-8)
      - Part 5, 1967 February 16 (Box-folder 12: 3, Box-folder 17: 19)
      - Part 6, 1967 March 1 (Box-folder 12: 4, Box-folder 17: 20)
      - Part 7, 1967 March 16 (Box-folder 12: 5, Box-folder 17: 21)
      - Part 8, 1967 April 1 (Box-folder 12: 6, Box-folder 15: 24-25)
    - Constituent Assembly list, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 8: 6)